Kelly Bearne

Leeds, West Yorkshire

kelly.b.tadcaster@gmail.com | 07826742123

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kbearne

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am a highly versatile and customer focused IT Specialist, with 12 years' experience working in a variety of roles within the industry. My career experience and 1st class degree (BSc (Hons) Computing and IT Practice) have provided knowledge and practical experience which I am always keen to put to good use and broaden.

KEY SKILLS

- Developing low code solutions in Microsoft Power Platform, which includes following agile development methodologies, attending daily sprints and utilisation of Azure DevOps
- Experience coding JavaScript, HTML5 and CSS3 (via Visual Studio Code IDE) to add functionality to a legacy CMS
- Continually updating my skills, including participating in courses such as CS50x, The Odin Project, and achieving Microsoft certifications in Power Platform
- Understanding of OOP and exposure to languages such as C, Java, C#
- Throughout my career I have organised/actioned requests received via busy inboxes, prioritising tasks where applicable and liaising effectively with staff.
- Experience consulting with and creating support documentation for both non-technical and technical staff.

EMPLOYMENT EXPERIENCE

IT Specialist, Dr. Oetker (September 2020 - Current)

Thorpe Park, 4600 Park Approach, Leeds, LS15 8GB

- Power Platform, SharePoint Online, Microsoft Teams and OneDrive configuration, administration and support (including the use of PowerShell)
- Developing low code solutions in Power Platform (including using SharePoint as a data source)
- Migration of data from SharePoint 2019 to SharePoint Online / Microsoft Teams / OneDrive using ShareGate and SPMT
- Responsible for managing 3rd line technical support requests from a global network, in the form of tickets, emails and telephone calls
- Providing training for end users via 1-2-1 sessions and group workshops
- Documentation creation (including refreshing an internal SharePoint knowledge base)
- Responding to incidents and events in accordance with set SLA and KPI's

Intranet Consultant, Turner & Townsend (May 2017 – August 2020)

Low Hall, Calverley Lane, Low Hall Road, Horsforth, LS18 4GH

- Maintaining and developing intranet pages and document libraries (involving the use of HTML, CSS and JavaScript)
- Maintaining search engine keywords for a large intranet (SharePoint Microsoft FAST)
- Compiling intranet and search engine analytics

- Organising and actioning requests submitted through a busy team inbox
- Liaising with other departments and customers
- Contributing towards and promoting intranet best practice and standards (including documentation)
- Contributing towards improving systems/tools and ways of working

Intranet Content Assistant, Turner & Townsend (June 2015 – May 2017)

Low Hall, Calverley Lane, Low Hall Road, Horsforth, LS18 4GH

- Maintaining and developing intranet pages and document libraries (involving the use of HTML, CSS and JavaScript)
- Maintaining search engine keywords for a large intranet (SharePoint Microsoft FAST)
- Compiling intranet and search engine analytics
- Organising and actioning requests submitted through a busy team inbox
- Liaising with other departments and customers
- Contributing towards and promoting intranet best practice and standards (including documentation)
- Contributing towards improving systems/tools and ways of working

Tape Validation Technician, Egton (EMIS) (August 2011 – June 2015)

Stafford House, Unit 2 Leathley Road, Hunslet, LS10 1BG

- Restoring and validating sensitive patient data securely (primarily for the NHS) using Backup Exec and SQL
- Working under pressure (regularly managing 25 servers)
- Documenting processes/best practice
- Onboarding new starters
- Liaising with departments across the business and external customers
- Managing and maintaining computer hardware and software for over 70 machines
- Configuring mobile devices (IOS and Android tablets) for GP practices

EDUCATION

Microsoft Certified: Power Platform App Maker Associate (December 2022)

Microsoft Certified: Power Platform Fundamentals (February 2021)

BSc (Hons) Computing and IT Practice (Top Up), Open University (September 2015 – September 2018)

First class honours achieved

Modules included E-business technologies, Software engineering, Web, mobile and cloud technologies and a final Computing and IT Project (for which I built a web application utilising MEAN stack and Bootstrap)

Microsoft Certified: Dynamics 365 Fundamentals (March 2020)

Google Analytics IQ certificate (January 2019)

ITIL Foundation Certificate, QA (April 2013)

Higher National Diploma Computing, Pembrokeshire College (September 2008 – June 2010) Merits and distinctions achieved for most modules; a wide range of subjects were covered

A Levels, Pembrokeshire College (September 2006 – July 2008)

A Level Double Applied ICT – CC

A Level History – C

GCSEs, Pembroke School (September 2000 – June 2005)

8 GCSEs, graded A* – C

PERSONAL INTERESTS

My interests include travel (particularly in Europe), technology, gaming and photography.